Guide to the Richard Hell Papers 1944-2003 (Bulk 1969-2003) MSS.140
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Photography
  - Subseries.A: Professional
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH close-up of face, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D6, Photo 9)
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH close-up, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D7, Photo 10)
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH and unidentified people sitting in room, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D8, Photo 11)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting in hallway with unidentified man, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D9, Photo 12)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing with three unidentified Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D10, Photo 13)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing on right of unidentified man, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D11, Photo 14)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing with arm around unidentified man, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D12, Photo 15)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing with arm around unidentified man, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D13, Photo 16)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH kneeling on ground, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D14, Photo 17)
    - B&W, 8"x10",, RH sitting against wall with unidentified man, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D15, Photo 18)
    - B&W, 8"x10",, RH standing with arm around unidentified woman, Photographer: S. Kay Young, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D16, Photo 19)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing on street in East Village, New York, Photographer: Godlis, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D17, Photo 20)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH head shot, Annotated on back: for RH, Photographer: Gin Saton, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D18, Photo 21)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing outside brick building with Acid Trash, Annotated on back: Hell is third from left, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D19, Photo 22)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH head shot, Annotated on back: Richard Hell, Photographer: Bob Gruen, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D20, Photo 23)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing in front of brick wall in black hat and suit with graffiti painted on wall, Photographer: Susan (Springfield) Beschta, Grafitti artist: Richard Hambleton, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D21, Photo 24)
    - negative of RH standing in front of brick wall in black hat and suit with graffiti painted on wall, Photographer: Susan (Springfield) Beschta, Grafitti artist: Richard Hambleton, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D22a, Photo 24a)
    - Color Polaroid, RH and The Voidoids in apartment, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D23, Photo 25)
    - Color Polaroid, RH and The Voidoids in apartment, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D23, Photo 26)
    - Color Polaroid, RH and The Voidoids in apartment, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D23, Photo 27)
    - Color Polaroid, RH and The Voidoids in apartment, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D23, Photo 28)
    - Color Polaroid, RH and The Voidoids in apartment, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D24, Photo 29)
    - Color, 2" x 2", Ivan Parker passport photo, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D25, Photo 30)
    - Color, 2" x 3.5", RH passport photo with border, RH wearing white shirt, black coat, and hair to shoulders, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D25, Photo 31)
    - Color, 2" x 2", Passport photo of man with long blond hair, checkered shirt and leather jacket, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D25, Photo 32)
    - Color, 2" x 2", Passport photo of man with short black hair and black t-shirt, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D25, Photo 33)
    - Color 4" x 6", 2 members of The Voidoids sitting on couch, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D26, Photo 34)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH and The Voidoids in apartment, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D27, Photo 35)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH and The Voidoids in apartment, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D27, Photo 35)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH and The Voidoids in apartment, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D27, Photo 36)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH and The Voidoids in apartment, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D27, Photo 37)
    - Color, 4"x 6", 2 band members of The Voidoids, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D28, Photo 38)
    - Color, 4"x 6", 2 band members of The Voidoids, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D28, Photo 39)
    - Color, 4"x 6",RH and The Voidoids in apartment, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D28, Photo 40)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH daughter (Ruby Meyers) and unidentified man, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D29, Photo 41)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified man, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D29, Photo 42)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with right arm around unidentified woman and man, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D30, Photo 43)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with right arm around unidentified woman and man, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D30, Photo 44)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with arm around unidentified man, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D31, Photo 45)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing with Sheelagh, and two unidentified men, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D31, Photo 46)
    - Color, 4"x 6",RH daughter (Ruby Meyers) sitting at table with RH books, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D31, Photo 47)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH daughter (Ruby Meyers) and unidentified woman, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D31, Photo 48)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified man and woman, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D32, Photo 29)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified man and woman, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D33, Photo 30)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified man and woman, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D34, Photo 31)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified woman, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D35, Photo 32)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified man (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D36, Photo 33)
    - Color, 4"x 6", 2 unidentified women, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D36, Photo 34)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing with unidentified man, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D37, Photo 35)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing with unidentified woman, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D38, Photo 36)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH and unidentified man in red shirt and black jacket, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D39, Photo 37)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing with right arm around grey haired unidentified man, with man in red shirt and another man with glasses, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D39, Photo 38)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified man in red dress shirt and black jacket and unidentified man in glasses, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D39, Photo 39)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with arms around three unidentified men, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D39, Photo 40)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing against aluminum door with Sheelagh and daughter, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D40, Photo 41)
    - Color, 4"x 6", Daughter (Ruby Meyers) with Sheelagh, RH and unidentified woman, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D40, Photo 42)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with unidentified woman and unidentified man in red shirt and black coat, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D40, Photo 43)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with daughter (Ruby Meyers) and unidentified woman, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D40, Photo 44)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing against brick wall wearing sunglasses, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D41, Photo 45)
    - Color, 4"x 6", Daughter (Ruby Meyers), Sheelagh, unidentified woman and man ,(2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D41, Photo 46)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with Sheelagh and daughter (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D41, Photo 47)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH with Sheelagh and daughter, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D41, Photo 48)
    - Color, 4"x 6", close-up of RH against brick wall, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D42, Photo 49)
    - Color, 4"x 6", Full body of RH standing against brick wall, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D42, Photo 50)
    - Color, 4"x 6", close-up of RH against brick wall, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D42, Photo 51)
    - Color, 4"x 6", close-up of RH against brick wall, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D42, Photo 52)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing in front of bookcase, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D43, Photo 53)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing in front of brick wall, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D44, Photo 54)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing in front of brick wall, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D45, Photo 55)
    - Color, 4"x 6", RH standing in front of brick wall, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D45, Photo 56)
    - B&W, 8"x11" contact sheet of 2"x3" photographs, RH promo shots, sitting, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D46, Photo 57)
    - B&W, 8"x11" contact sheet of 2"x3" photographs, RH promo shots, sitting, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D46, Photo 58)
    - B&W, 5" x 7", RH promotional photo for GO NOW, Photographer: Melanie Wiener, (2), undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D47, Photo 59)
    - Sepia, 3" x 9" contact sheet of 2.5" x 2.5" photos, RH sitting on wood box next to old fashioned gas station pump, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D48, Photo 60)
    - B&W, 3" x 4" photocopy of RH headshot, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E1, Photo 1)
    - B&W, 7.5" X 9", photocopy of page 29 and page 30 of book, Theresa Stern composite on the front with title: Wanna Go Out? and text on pages, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E2, Photo 2)
    - B&W, 5.5" x 9", photocopy, RH sitting on couch, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E3, Photo 3)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", pencil drawing of cropping instructions for RH and band members, instructions at top read “Make negative of 8x10 and …" with RH removed and blown up to 11x14 crop, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E4, Photo 4)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", photocopy of article from THE SOHO WEEKLY NEWS, titled “Television: Escapees from Heaven", Jun 27, 1974 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E5, Photo 5)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph, Tom Verlaine, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E6, Photo 6)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph, RH standing in front of brick player, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E7, Photo 7)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph (3" x 4") of RH sitting with arms crossed, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E8, Photo 8)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph, unidentified woman standing, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E9, Photo 9)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph, RH with black pants and sunglasses, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E10, Photo 10)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph, RH with gun, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E11, Photo 11)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph, (5"x7"), RH with The Voidoids, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E12, Photo 12)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph, RH and the Voidoids, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E13, Photo 13)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph (3" x 3"), RH and Tom Verlaine, RH holding Theresa Stern composite, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E14, Photo 14)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of drawing of half of RH’s face, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E15, Photo 15)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of two quotes, one by Paul Bowles, Without Stopping and the second by Isabelle Eberhardt, The Oblivion Seekers (translated by Paul Bowles), From The East Village Eye, Oct 1979 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E16, Photo 16)
    - B&W, 4" x 4.5", Circle design with instructions: Reduce 1 ½" inches and ¼ in., undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E17, Photo 17)
    - B&W, 5" x 4.5", Circle design enlarged, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E17, Photo 18)
    - B&W, 4" x 5", circle design in white on black background, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E17, Photo 19)
    - B&W, 5.5" x 9" on cardstock, 1997 year long calendar card with image of man wearing hat and holding balloons, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E18, Photo 20)
    - B&W, 6.5" x 9", newspaper clipping titled Richard Hell by Beate Nilsen, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E19, Photo 21)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of photograph (6" x 8"), RH headshot, cropped with orange pencil around his face, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E20, Photo 22)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", Photocopy of article titled Red Red Quine, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E21, Photo 23)
    - Article from The Virginian Pilot and The Ledger -Star, titled Southern Feminism, about RH’s mother, by Mike D’Orso, May 10, 1985 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E21a, Photo 23a)
    - Photo 24 B&W, 8"x11", Promotional flyer of Richard Hell from Singer Management, 4 copies, 1982 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E22, Photo 24)
    - ‘Lifestyles of the Poor and Famous," article from the Voice, Sep 17, 1985 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E22a, Photo 24a)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", Richard Hell in striped shirt and black pants looking at camera, full body shot, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E23, Photo 25)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11",Richard Hell in polka dot shirt and holding guitar, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E24, Photo 26)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E25, Photo 27)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", Dark Photo of RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E26, Photo 28)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", of RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E27, Photo 29)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E28, Photo 30)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH and The Voidoids RH, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E29, Photo 31)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11",RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E30, Photo 32)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", dark photo of RH and The Voidoids, RH in white shirt squatting on the ground, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E31, Photo 33)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH and the Voidoids, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E32, Photo 34)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11",RH with ripped black shirt with colored triangles, sunglasses, holding guitar, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E33, Photo 35)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH wearing striped shirt and black pants looking up at camera, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E34, Photo 36)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11",RH wearing striped shirt and black pants, sunglasses, and looking at camera, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E35, Photo 37)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11",RH with half lit face, ripped black t-shirt with triangles design, holding guitar, looking at camera, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E36, Photo 38)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH with The Voidoids, RH wearing yellow long sleeve shirt, smoking cigarette and looking to left of camera, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E37, Photo 39)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH in red shirt and wearing gold chain, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E38, Photo 40)
    - Photocopy, Color, 8"x11", RH and Band wearing white shirt and sitting on stool, looking at camera, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E39, Photo 41)
    - B&W, 8"x11", unidentified woman sitting on floor with cigarette looking at wall, titled: “Insomniac", Photographer: Babette Meyers, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E40, Photo 42)
    - B&W, 8"x11", Richard Hell figurine in silhouette, standing on wood floor, Photographer: Babette Meyers, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E41, Photo 43)
    - B&W, 8"x11", unidentified woman in white dress against wood wall covered in shadow from lattice, Photographer: Babette Meyers, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E42, Photo 44)
    - B&W, 8"x11", Three dolls, top is RH, then Tibetan doll, and then blond girl doll with legs spread, titled “False Idols," Babette Meyers, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E43, Photo 45)
    - B&W, 8"x11", Unidentified woman, Photographer: [Babette Meyers], undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E44, Photo 46)
    - B&W, 8"x11", unidentified woman, titled “Jesus Christ, it’s Christmas Again", Photographer: Babette Meyers, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E45, Photo 47)
    - B&W, 8"x11", negative of woman in leopard bathing suit, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E46, Photo 48)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH in knee length coat and sunglasses standing in Italian street, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E47, Photo 49)
    - B&W, 4" x 6" view looking up to ceiling of cathedral, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E47, Photo 50)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", photo of Mickey and Minnie Mouse with Goofy holding a EU flag, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E47, Photo 51)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", Top three floors of square building, antennas on roof, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E47, Photo 52)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH wearing sunglasses, smiling and wearing sunglasses, standing in front of stone wall, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E47, Photo 53)
    - B&W, 4" x 6",Close-up of RH wearing sunglasses and smoking, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E48, Photo 54)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", Photo of statue, man holding cross, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E48, Photo 55)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH standing in front of statue of skull and bones, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E48, Photo 56)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", inside of restaurant, chef wearing white hat looking at camera, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E49, Photo 57)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", close-up of RH, with out sunglasses, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E49, Photo 58)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH standing in front of fountain, Piazza Vecchia, Florence, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E49, Photo 59)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", statue of man falling backwards, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E49, Photo 60)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", Woman on bridge, looking over left shoulder, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E50, Photo 61)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH in jacket and sunglasses, looking at camera, trees and stone house in buildings in background, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E50, Photo 62)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH in jacket and sunglasses, looking at camera, hand on hip, trees and stone house in buildings in background, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E50, Photo 63)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", Woman standing in front of fountain and clock, Piazza Vecchio, Florence, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E50, Photo 64)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH standing in front of fountain and clock, Florence, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E51, Photo 65)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH sitting down wearing sunglasses, white t-shirt, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E51, Photo 66)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", unidentified woman in restaurant sitting and side view of man, waiter in white uniform and hat, Italy, Piazza Vecchio, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E51, Photo 67)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", close-up of RH without sunglasses, looking at camera, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E51, Photo 68)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", unidentified woman wearing black top in front of fountain, Piazza Vecchio, Florence, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E52, Photo 69)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", RH standing in front of fountain and statues, Piazza Vecchio, Florence, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E52, Photo 70)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", unidentified woman in black standing with stone building and trees in background, Florence, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E52, Photo 71)
    - B&W, 4" x 6", unidentified woman, face and neck, in between building, Florence, Italy, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E52, Photo 72)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", RH and Patty Smyth, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E53, Photo 73)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", RH and baby, both smiling, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E54, Photo 74)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", RH holding baby and looking at camera, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E55, Photo 75)
    - B&W, 8" x 11", RH and baby on couch, RH on phone, undated (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeve E56, Photo 76)
    - 35 sleeves, containing 35 millimeter slides, color 3x5" snapshots, 8x10" black and white prints, 35mm negatives and contact sheets, photographer: Bob Gruen, 1988 (Box Binder F)
  - Subseries: B Personal Photography
    Collected photographs of Richard Hell's friends and family. Prints and negatives interfiled. Arranged chronologically.
    - Six Polaroid images, RH and unidentified woman, May 1966-Jan 1968 (Box Binder G, Folder a.)
    - 10 sleeves,, 3 x 5 color and B&W 35mm prints, 8x10 B&W, RH and unidentified woman,, close-ups of unidentified woman, color polaroids, B&W photo booth strip of RH and unidentified woman, wedding photographs, 1980s (Box Binder G, Folder b.)
    - 24 sleeves, 3x5 35mm prints, 8x10 black and white prints, photo booth strip and contact sheet, RH and Patty Smyth and baby photos of Ruby, Photographer Roberta Bayley, 1985-1990 (Box Binder G, Folder c.)
    - 9 sleeves, contact sheets and negatives, RH and unidentified woman, 1987 (Box Binder G, Folder d.)
    - 24 sleeves, color 3x5 35mm prints, color Polaroid, RH and family (Ruby, Patty Smyth, and unidentified others), 1987-1991 (Box Binder G, Folder e.)
    - 3 sleeves, B&W 8x10 photos, RH and unidentified others, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski, c. 1994. (Box Binder H, Folder a.)
    - 6 sleeves, Color 4x6 photos of Gettysburg "dead ends", Lexington Kentucky, letter from J. Justice, 2002 (Box Binder H, Folder b.)
    - 18 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, one color 8x10 of W.Burroughs, RH and Sheelagh on road trip to Kansas, visiting William Burroughs, 1990s (Box Binder H, Folder c.)
    - 22 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, 3 color 5x7 prints of RH and Sheelagh, photo booth strip, RH, Ruby, Sheelagh, and unidentified others in various locations, late 1990's to early 2000's., ca.2000 (Box Binder H, Folder d.)
    - 5 sheets, B&W 8x10 prints of RH and unidentified woman, contact sheets and negatives of unidentified people, undated (Box Binder H, Folder e.)
    - 4 sleeves, color Polaroid images of RH and Sheelagh, undated (Box Binder H, Folder f.)
    - 5 sleeves, B&W 4x6, 5x7, 8x10 prints of unidentified man, Ruby and RH, undated (Box Binder H, Folder g.)
    - 8 sleeves, photo booth strip, 3x5 color photos, RH and Ruby, Sheelagh, and unidentified others in various locations, undated (Box Binder H, Folder h.)
    - 57 sleeves, color 4x6 photos, color 3x 12 photos, contact sheet, letter, Wedding Photos of RH and Sheelagh, 2002 (Box Binder I, Folder a.)
    - 14 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negative, art objects, RH and Ruby, Sheelagh and unidentified others, ca.2001 (Box Binder J, Folder a.)
    - 11 sleeves, color, 4x6 photos and negatives, RH and Ruby, Halloween and other dates, ca.1995 (Box Binder J, Folder b.)
    - 9 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, RH close-ups, Sheelagh, NYC, undated (Box Binder J, Folder c.)
    - 16 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, RH, Sheelagh and Ruby, on beach, Ruby at school, various locations, undated (Box Binder J, Folder d.)
    - 9 sleeves, color 4x6 photos and negatives, RH and Ruby, Ruby's birthday party, 1994-2001 (Box Binder J, Folder e.)